<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Your Twitch sword</string>
    <string name="title_activity_about_tab">AboutTab</string>
    <string name="About">About</string>
    <string name="ethaddr" translatable="false">0x55dF1Ea2933AEb271fFae56AE8f464A5AC23a3b1</string>
    <string name="SocialMedia">Socials medias</string>
    <string name="chosenewchannel">Chose an other channel</string>
    <string name="legal">Legal</string>
    <string name="legalcontent">Icons : \nmaterial.io \nwww.flaticon.com/authors/pixel-perfect
        \n\nLibrary: \ngithub.com/studioidan/HttpAgent</string>
    <string name="connectionErrorHTML">Impossible connection</string>
    <string name="twitchUnjoinableHTML">Impossible to join Twitch\'s server ; verify your internet connection, and restart the app</string>
    <string name="save">Save</string>
    <string name="channelname">Name of the channel to join</string>
    <string name="name">Name</string>
    <string name="connect">Connect</string>
    <string name="errorchannelvoid">Please enter a channel name</string>
    <string name="reason">Reason</string>
    <string name="dayin1letter">d</string>
    <string name="weekin1letter">w</string>
    <string name="aboutdev">About dev</string>
    <string name="aboutapp">About App</string>
    <string name="appexplainations">This app is an app to help you to apply your moderation rights
        on a Twitch chat. The first advantage of this app, is the UI : with it, you\'ll almost never
        need to take your keyboard (only for typing reasons of TO/Ban), and you\'ll never have to
        write "/timeout", "/ban" or "!permit" anymore, just tap on two buttons. The second
        advantage, is the multiple selection : you can ban almost as much users as you want in only
        one tap (As a moderator, Twitch keeps you to send more than 100 messages/commands per 30
        seconds, be sure to send less without what you\'ll be timeout from all Twitch.tv for 30
        minutes… I may add an indicator in the next update). And the last but not least, YOU chose
        when chat moves (at least on app), and it\'s useful on very active chatrooms… it prevent
        from ban random people just because the chat moves too quickly\n
        Last thing: the app shows an object for each users, only the last message is shown, so I
        encourage you to use it beside your computer without what you\'ll not see spam…
        \n\nUsage:\n
        Tap on user(s) that you want to Ban/TO/Permit, set the reason and the time (with the slider
        at the top of the screen) if needed, and tap on the action you want to preform
        (Ban/Permit/TO).\n
        Tip : if you don\'t find the right Timeout duration, put the slider far
        right, and you\'ll be able to set your custom timeout.
    </string>
</resources>
