<resources>
    <string name="app_name">TO Box</string>
    <string name="title_activity_about_tab">AboutTab</string>
    <string name="About">About</string>
    <string name="ethaddr" translatable="false">0x55dF1Ea2933AEb271fFae56AE8f464A5AC23a3b1</string>
    <string name="SocialMedia">Socials medias</string>
    <string name="chosenewchannel">Chose an other channel</string>
    <string name="legal">Legal</string>
    <string name="legalcontent">Icons : \nmaterial.io\nwww.flaticon.com/authors/pixel-perfect
        \n\nLibrary used: \ngithub.com/studioidan/HttpAgent\n\nLicences:\nAll icons/logos/trademark
        own to their respective owners, even if they aren\'t mentioned bellow\n
        Twitch logo, Twitch trademark, \"Glitch\", and all other resources that fit in intellectual property of Twitch, are property of Twitch.tv, service owned by Amazon.com, Inc.\n
        YouTube logo, trademark, and all other resources that fit in intellectual property of Youtube, are property of YouTube, LLC. owned by Alphabet Inc. (Google)\n
        Octocat (Github logo), and all other resources that fit in intellectual property of Github, are property of GitHub, Inc.\n
        PayPal trademark, and all other resources that fit in intellectual property of PayPal, are property of PayPal Holdings, Inc.\n\n

        (If there is any issue with what\'s wrote above (ex: company name misspelled; something
        that\'s in your property or your organisation property, appear in app or in the source code
        but not above; name or logo that doesn\'t appear like you want (like (tm) or © missing); bad
        attributions of some resources; or any other kind of legal issue) please contact me thought
        my email address given on Github or on the Play store page of the app, before engage
        procedures, so I can fix this issue, I\'m a beginner with publishing apps or legal issues in
        general so it\'s certainly not perfect… sorry)
    </string>
    <string name="connectionErrorHTML">Impossible connection</string>
    <string name="twitchUnjoinableHTML">Impossible to join Twitch\'s server ; verify your internet connection, and restart the app</string>
    <string name="save">Save</string>
    <string name="channelname">Name of the channel to join</string>
    <string name="name">Name</string>
    <string name="connect">Connect</string>
    <string name="errorchannelvoid">Please enter a channel name</string>
    <string name="reason">Reason</string>
    <string name="dayin1letter">d</string>
    <string name="weekin1letter">w</string>
    <string name="aboutdev">About dev</string>
    <string name="aboutapp">About App</string>
    <string name="appexplainations">This app is an app to help you to apply your moderation rights
        on a Twitch chat. The first advantage of this app, is the UI : with it, you\'ll almost never
        need to take your keyboard (only for typing reasons of TO/Ban), and you\'ll never have to
        write "/timeout", "/ban" or "!permit" anymore, just tap on two buttons. The second
        advantage, is the multiple selection : you can ban almost as much users as you want in only
        one tap (As a moderator, Twitch keeps you to send more than 100 messages/commands per 30
        seconds, be sure to send less without what you\'ll be timeout from all Twitch.tv for 30
        minutes… I may add an indicator in the next update). And the last but not least, YOU chose
        when chat moves (at least on app), and it\'s useful on very active chatrooms… it prevent
        from ban random people just because the chat moves too quickly\n
        Last thing: the app shows an object for each users, only the last message is shown, so I
        encourage you to use it beside your computer without what you\'ll not see spam…
        \n\nUsage:\n
        Tap on user(s) that you want to Ban/TO/Permit, set the reason and the time (with the slider
        at the top of the screen) if needed, and tap on the action you want to preform
        (Ban/Permit/TO).\n
        Tip : if you don\'t find the right Timeout duration, put the slider far
        right, and you\'ll be able to set your custom timeout.
    </string>
    <string name="mypapayladress">Or my PayPal address : matt2001@hotmail.fr</string>
</resources>
